export const insights = [
	{
		title: 'AULT Overview',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'What Is AULT?',
				answer:
					'AULT is an exclusive concierge service designed to provide seamless access to gold-backed financial services, allowing the purchase, management, and spend of gold assets securely, with flexibility and ease.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Why Gold?',
				answer:
					'Gold is a stable, long-term asset with a proven track record of preserving value across economic fluctuations. Unlike traditional currencies or investments, gold offers a tangible hedge against uncertainty and market volatility, providing security and liquidity.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Is AULT an Investment Product?',
				answer:
					'No, AULT does not offer investment services. It provides means to convert your fiat currency into gold and gives you real-time access to your gold assets whenever you need them.'
			},
			{
				question: 'What Are The Benefits Of AULT’s Gold-Backed Services?',
				answer:
					'Gold is a stable, long-term asset with a proven track record of preserving value across economic fluctuations. Unlike traditional currencies or investments, gold offers a tangible hedge against uncertainty and market volatility, providing security and liquidity.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Getting Started with AULT',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'What Do I Need To Get Started?',
				answer:
					'To start using AULT, simply convert your fiat currency (USD, GBP, NGN etc.) into gold through our network. Once the conversion is done, you can spend your gold using the AULT Mastercard.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Can I Use My Local Currency (NGN)?',
				answer:
					'Yes, you can use NGN. AULT will convert your local currency into gold at the prevailing exchange rate, and we will handle all the conversion details for you.'
			},
			{
				question: 'How Long Does It Take To Set Up My Account?',
				answer:
					'Once your AULT account is set up and minimum funding amount is availed, gold is purchased within one business day. It typically takes between one to four weeks to receive your AULT Mastercard.'
			},
			{
				question: 'How Do I Fund My AULT Account?',
				answer:
					'You can fund your AULT account by transferring fiat currency (USD, GBP, NGN etc.) to our trustee partner. Once the funds are received, we will convert them into gold on your behalf.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Leasing & Credit Insights',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'What is gold leasing with AULT?',
				answer:
					'Gold leasing allows you to earn returns by temporarily lending your allocated gold, while maintaining ownership and flexibility.'
			},
			{
				question: 'How does leasing generate returns?',
				answer:
					'When you lease your gold, it is used within trusted financial markets, and you receive interest or income from that arrangement — all while your gold remains securely stored.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Can I access credit using my gold?',
				answer:
					'Yes. You can access flexible credit by using your gold as collateral. Empowering you to borrow up to 50% the value of your assets instead of spending it.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Accessing and Spending Your Gold',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'How Do I Access My Gold?',
				answer:
					'Once your account is active, your gold is stored securely in LBMA-certified and insured vaults in London, audited monthly by KPMG LLP. You can access it via the AULT web app and use it as currency through your AULT Mastercard.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Do I Need To Sell My Gold To Spend It?',
				answer:
					'No, you don’t need to sell your gold. AULT has partnered with regulated financial entities, which provide you with a payment card that allows you to spend your gold directly, anywhere in the world.'
			},
			{
				question: 'How Does AULT Ensure My Gold’s Value?',
				answer:
					"AULT’s platform provides real-time access to your gold’s value and tracks the global gold market trends. You’ll receive regular updates through the AULT app to monitor your assets' performance."
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Security and Safeguards',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'How Is My Gold Stored?',
				answer:
					'Your gold is stored securely as insured allocated investment-grade London Good Delivery bars, sitting in London vaults. These vaults are vetted and meet international standards of security and compliance.'
			},
			{
				question: 'What Safeguards Are In Place To Protect My Gold?',
				answer:
					'AULT works with authorized legal entities and regulated financial services partners to ensure the highest security for your assets. We also have a regulated trustee, Emerging Africa, providing fiduciary oversight to ensure your gold is handled with care.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Mastercard and Additional Benefits',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'What Is World Elite?',
				answer:
					'World Elite is a premium Mastercard offering exclusive benefits such as luxury travel perks, concierge services, airport lounge access, and more. With your AULT Mastercard, you gain access to these privileges globally.'
			},
			{
				question: 'What Are The Benefits Of The AULT Mastercard?',
				answer:
					'Access to Mastercard Travel & Lifestyle Concierge\nVIP airport lounge access for you and a guest\nDiscounts on luxury travel, hotels, and car rentals\nTravel insurance coverage, including up to $500,000 for medical emergencies\nRental car insurance for theft, damage, and loss'
			},
			{
				question: 'What Happens If I Lose My AULT Mastercard?',
				answer:
					'With access to the AULT web app, you may change the pin or block the stolen card. You may also contact your relationship manager at AULT and upon request, we will block the card and issue a replacement to ensure your funds remain secure.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'General Information',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'How Do I Track My Gold and Its Value?',
				answer:
					'AULT offers a secure app where you can view your gold assets, their current value, and real-time market trends. This dashboard allows you to track your investments and manage your gold easily.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Where Is AULT Registered?',
				answer:
					'AULT is a UK & Nigeria registered entity, adhering to international standards for financial security and compliance.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Can I Sell My Gold And Receive Fiat Currency?',
				answer:
					'Yes, if you wish to liquidate your gold to fiat, this means you have chosen to close your AULT account. This will require a 3-month notice and a date of refund will be communicated. All refunds will go to the account the funds initially came from.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Does AULT Operate In Other Markets?',
				answer:
					'AULT is currently expanding its services and plans to offer additional asset solutions in various global markets in the coming years.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Does AULT Provide Ongoing Support?',
				answer:
					'Yes, AULT offers ongoing support to our clients. Our team is available anytime to assist with your account or answer any questions you may have.'
			},
			{
				question: 'What Are The Minimum And Maximum Amounts For Gold Purchase?',
				answer:
					'The minimum amount for gold purchase depends on if it is a first-time purchase or a subsequent purchase. AULT will provide the full details during registration.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Can I Jointly Own Gold With Someone?',
				answer:
					'Yes, if this person or these people are members of the same organization e.g. family office or trust company. More information can be provided on request.'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		title: 'Fees, Charges, and Account Management',
		items: [
			{
				question: 'Where Can I Use My AULT Mastercard?',
				answer:
					'You can use your AULT Mastercard anywhere Mastercard is accepted, globally, allowing you to spend your gold assets in any currency.'
			},
			{
				question: 'Are There Any Fees Associated With AULT?',
				answer:
					'Yes, AULT charges a monthly custody fee for account maintenance. Full details of any fees will be provided during the registration process so you can be fully informed.'
			}
		]
	},
];
